they just started High fiveing each
other talking mad for me like yo my
little cousin got balls my little
cousin's a g my cousin ain't scared of
nobody Brooklyn got the Batman now the
baby's coming it's
[Music]
[Applause]
coming
[Music]
[Applause]
w a host of his own podcast called
Stoops the stages please give it up for
gastor miti everybody let him
he
so I'm from East New York you know and
and when you grow up in East New York
you tend to have a bit of a edge to you
you know um as an example of that uh
this past Thanksgiving you know my uncle
came up to me he's like yo gasta you
know your father once stabed somebody
over
Snapple and then he just walked
away like you know that's how you end
conversations there's no more details I
want to that apparently people die with
fruit punch all the
time but it occurred to me that my
father just never wanted me to know that
side of him you know he was trying real
hard to protect me and he came up with
this plan he decided you know what I'm
going to buy a house with my sister
I'mma buy an next door to my other
sister you know we could Shield him from
the neighborhood and it was smart you
know I have my mom my dad my aunt
upstairs is my all next door and
together they could kind of keep me from
the hoodlums in the area you know
protect me but the problem was is that
my cousins that lived upstairs and next
door they were the hoodlums in the
area you know I was I was 5 years old my
cousin Mito is 14 lived upstairs my
cousin Carlos is 15 next door you know
and it was a challenge because they were
cold as
like Teenage drug dealers are
amazing
you got to understand every day I'm
going to school these dudes teenage drug
dealers are real prot treny they don't
care about
schedules they don't do unless they
want to you know so I'm seeing this
every day and I wanted to take part but
I couldn't cuz caros Ando got into this
real shitty habit you know of scaring
the out of
me all the time you know they had this
like pale white face face mask with
green hair look like the Joker and they
used to put it on and hop up from behind
walls and scream in my face wasn't cool
I don't appreciate laughing at that
man they did this relentlessly they
would screaming my face I'd run inside
crying my mom would hug me she'd tell my
dad my dad would go outside he'd scream
at them to cut the and they' leave
me alone for a couple weeks we had a
system and this went on for like a year
you know and I was okay with that but
the problem is you know I was about to
turn six week of my birthday lands
during Halloween week you know and my
father believed two things he said one
I'm 6 years old he thought that I should
be able to handle these things on my own
and two they were 15 to 16 years old at
this point they're still young enough
where they could get away with wearing
mask so in the week where I should be
thrilled I'm getting older I'm scared
cuz my dad gave these two gangsters cart
blanch to scare the out of
me oh God damn weak ain't
cool despite that I woke up in a good
mood my mom made
pancakes crushing it in school too my 2
plus two game is
crazy nobody was seeing me I felt good
was dressed up I walk out the apartment
door got to the front door of the
building you know and meito was opening
the door for me cuz he lived upstairs
you know got up early to cheer me up he
said happy birthday little man I said yo
you be being strangely polite to
Leo I don't know what brought about this
but keep it up I like
it and I walked out the door cheery as
and Carlos jumps out from the side
got the mask on screens on my face he's
like bold I'm like oh and I run
inside screaming and I hear the door
closed and he laugh in the background
happy birthday
I get
inside my mom hugs me my dad walks in
from my side he was waiting in the car
and he's like what happened I'm like
Carlos and meito they scared me and he's
like yo man up handle your
business right it sound like solid
advice but that's what he said about
everything you know say yo Pops how the
time I shoot man up in handle your
business it was a gangster with one
proverb you
know and I'm like yo Pops I need your
help here man he's like what happened
I'm like caros Ando they scared me how
do they scare you Gast though they
scared me with the mask what kind of
mask is it it's a joker mask pops you
not paying attention to what's happening
in these
streets I need your help out here my G
it's
real he's like calm down
gastar who's the Joker scared
of I said Batman
pops so he said why don't you be Batman
I said that's a good
idea and I believe that in my heart
he gave my mom some cash we went to City
Line for those you non New Yorker City
Line is the border of Brooklyn and
Queens it's a nice shopping area now but
back then it was a foot lock and a bunch
of 99 Cent Stores you know and we went
out there to buy a costume you know I'm
I got kids I spent $65 this year on my
son's costume so you could be Captain
America it's
I told my wife I'm spending $65
he better be Captain America for
graduation New Year's Day I want to see
this in
rotation this is not what I got though I
got a plastic mask it had a white rubber
band it went
around lips was white so I look like
I'll buy no Batman all
year you know but I pulled that off
I was proud you know next day I woke up
I walked outside and they scared me and
I ain't going to front still ran inside
crying my mom grabbed me she said Gast
St hold up baby stick to the plan I said
you right Mom
y'all crushing this parenting thing by
the
way go keep that up man and I went to my
room I put the mask on and I started
taking off my clothes CU I had the
Batman underwear you know had the full
Ensemble but I turned them around cuz
the logo was on the ass part I want them
to know I meant
business you know you got to see it
coming so I went to the in front of the
building you know and I open the door
call some meito was chatting with they
boys I did the you know superhero pose
and
y' I'm Batman and I ain't scared of
you no
more and they just started
laughing which was fine cuz I could see
Migo's face but caros still had the
Joker mask on and I don't know if you
seen the movies when Joker laughs some
real shit's about to go
down it occurred to me I hadn't thought
through this
plan
but they just started high-fiving each
other talking mad for me they like
yo my little cousin got balls my little
cousins a g my cousin ain't scared of
nobody Brooklyn got the on Batman
now that felt great man I got cocky as
I was in the gang now I'm in I went
to school talking mad that day told
all my classmates hey yo listen some
go down don't worry about it I got
you covered I can't explain cuz I got to
take off my clothes
but trust me it's under
control you know now what I didn't
realize is when you tell this plan to to
your cousins every time they were bored
which apparently is all the time for
Teenage drug
dealers they will come up with wild
for me to
solve they like yo yo my pet rockweiler
got stuck in the aband the building go
get Brooklyn
Batman Yo Miss Brown she's hallucinating
again get Brooklyn
Batman yo the competing drug dealers
they on our block man get Brooklyn
Batman I ain't solve that last
one but I was entertaining enough for
them to end it amicably point being is I
was
effective you know but this went on for
a while my rep was now starting to get
out there I was sitting in class my last
name's alonte it starts with a ace I
always had that front seat by the door
and the kids would walk by the door and
I would hear them one kid was like yo
that's that kid that think he
Batman and the other kid would jump in
no that kid is
Batman you know was real out there
but this is stressful they don't tell
you this you got to be Batman all
the time he don't get no days
off like ever I got to do I'm in
school
be 3+ 3 is next week like this is
hard be I'm stressed I told my dad's yo
Pops I can't be Batman no more man it's
just too much work I need something easy
like you got with this parenting
thing and he's like listen gas store you
got over your feed mego and Carlos
leaving you alone you can put the mask
way it's not that serious and that's
what I did I retired The Mask I stopped
being
Batman and that should have been the end
of it right but superhero's life is
never
easy now it's 15 my dad bought a few
more houses you know we we moved away
but we decided to go back to visit my
aunts to lived upstairs Carlos has gone
to
jail Meo moved down south to avoid some
problems I can't get into that
here but he decided to come up to visit
little family occasion and I go up to
mangito like yo
mangito not for nothing but why would
you keep scaring the out of me with
this damn mask all the time and he's
like yo that wasn't even an idea that
was your dad
excuse
me he said yeah he came up to us when we
when he bought the house and he was like
listen I don't care if y'all are
hustling in front of my house just make
sure my son never want to hang out with
you
guys and they interpreted that as let's
scare the out of this little kid
every
day and I talked to my dad about I like
yo Pops is true you scaring me
on purpose he's like yeah but it worked
right and I learned two things I learned
One turns out wasn't even a joker mask
it was a Beetlejuice
mask I'm not scared of the joker I'm
scared of Tim Burton
movies you know I found out recently
it's the same dude playing both
characters I was Michael ke and fight
fting Michael
[Applause]
Keon but the second thing I realized
this whole time I was trying to be
Batman my dad is Batman he didn't want
any of the credit he just wanted to get
done he wanted it solved that
was beautiful to me you know and now as
an adult you know we we work together a
lot we have a good relationship about a
month back he came over to my house
apparently uh one of my tenants they had
a break in um and this is the building
that I live in so he went over before I
did I was at work he went to console my
wife told her about what we were going
to do to you know fortify the home make
her feel comfortable and I get home and
he's like yo gastor come over here for a
second and we walk into my daughter's
room to get some privacy and he's like
yo when when the robbers came in why
ain't you or your wife get the ratchet
I'm like yo pop I'm not a
rapper I don't know what the ratchet is
man and then he just casually walked
over to the wall he banged the window
pain and the machete came out then he
went over to the heater went reached
underneath and he pulled out a
gun the ratchet gastor I said yo pop
it's my house you got had a gun in my
house and he's like Gast I keep a gun in
every
house I'm like but this is my daughter's
room and he's like I
know you're
welcome this whole time I wanted to
be Batman it turns out I'm
Alfred and I felt real touch that Batman
finally decided to reveal himself to me
thank
you